

Mike Peters

Senior Digital Designer

- 678.858.6863
- mikepeters.io

ABOUT

I'm a dedicated and creative web professional with nearly a decade of experience ranging from print design and the CMYK process to user interfaces and front-end web development.

I believe good design is always in service of the user and it's my job to ensure that a project achieves both its business objectives and the needs of its users above all else.

SOCIAL

- Bē behance.net/mikeio
- in linkedin.com/in/mikepetersio/
- github.com/mikeio

EXPERIENCE

Force Marketing

2015 - 2017

Senior Digital Designer

Atlanta, GA

Interactive Team

- Produced high-quality websites and applications, including user interfaces, sitemaps, wireframes and visual designs based on requirements.
- ▶ Developed mobile-friendly and responsive HTML products utilizing HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- ▶ Produced designs for interactive marketing materials, landing pages, e-mails campaigns and digital advertisements.
- Collaborated with various internal and external teams such as PHP and .Net developers as well as SEM and SEO teams.

Brightfire

2012 - 2015

Web Designer

Lawrenceville, GA

- Worked directly with Live Nation and managed creative assets for multiple markets; specifically Live Nation Atlanta, Florida and the national market.
- Daily responsibilities included the creation of websites, applications, digital advertisements as well as print items such as posters, handbills, billboards and large format printed items.

RSVPATL 2010 - 2012

Graphic Designer

Atlanta, GA

- Produced quality work in a fast-paced environment, meeting deadlines and client expectations for creativity and accuracy.
- Created branding for multiple clients including web sites, logo design, brochures, postcards, billboards and business cards.
- Helped clients revitalize their online presence using content management systems, event management software, social media platforms and digital advertising.



APPLICATIONS

- Adobe Photoshop
- ▶ Adobe Illustrator
- ▶ Adobe InDesign
- ▶ Sketch
- Sublime Text
- Codekit
- ▶ MAMP

SKILLS

- Advanced knowledge of HTML, CSS and preprocessor languages like SASS.
- Extensive knowledge of the Foundation and Bootstrap frameworks.
- Knowledge of version control systems such as Github and Bitbucket.
- Working knowledge of PHP and Javascript.

Neighborhood News

Junior Graphic Designer

2005 - 2007 Dacula, GA

Worked closely with the sales staff to create, modify and update advertisements in time to meet monthly advertising deadlines.

Worked directly with the editorial staff to design and build the monthly newspaper.

EDUCATION

▶ Art Institute of Atlanta

2007 - 2010

Graphic & Web Design

Atlanta, GA

George Walton Academy

1994 - 2005

High School Diploma

Monroe, GA

AWARDS

▶ HipChat

2013

Best of Week 4 Winner

T-Shirt Contest

https://blog.hipchat.com/2013/07/16/hipchat-t-shirt-contest-best-of-week-4/

Transworld Skateboarding

2011

1st Place Winner

Pay Day: Wes Kremer

http://skateboarding.transworld.net/

US Achievement Academy

2004

All American Scholar Award

Journalism

http://www.usaa-academy.com/